Ngo Phu Huu Dai **Son**

COMPUTER SCIENCE STUDENT

583, Tổ 7, ấp Tân Thuận, xã Tân Nhuận Đông, Châu Thành, Đồng Tháp

□ (+84) 79-3979-011 | ■ ngodaisonn@gmail.com | □ IrisStream | □ son-ngo-phu-huu-dai-93a07a215

"Be the change that you want to see in the world."

Summary _

I'm a computer Science student at Ho Chi Minh University of Science. Good knowlegde in Data structure and algorithm. 7+ years experience in competitive programming. Super nerd who loves Vim, Linux and using terminal and enjoys to customize all of the development environment. Interested in devising a better problem-solving method for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools if the need arises.

Education

HCMUS(Ho Chi Minh University of Science)

HCMC, Vietnam

Aug. 2018 - ...

BACHELOR STUDENT IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

· GPA: 8.11/10

Skill

Hard Skill

SOME TECHNICAL SKILLS

- ·• C/C++
- '• PYTHON
- '• DATA STRUCTURES
- '• ALGORITHMS
- '• MATH

- '• GIT/GITHUB
- '• RESEARCH
- '• VIM
- '• MS SQL SERVER
- '• FAMILIAR WITH LINUX OPERATION SYSTEM

Soft Skill

SOME SOCIAL SKILLS

- * TEAMWORK
- * TIME MANAGEMENT
- '• CRITICAL THINKING
- '• SEFT LEARNING

Honors & Awards

2019 **Second Prize**, HCMUS Student Informatics Olympic Competition

HCMC, Vietnam

2018 **Semi Final**, HCMUS The bravery of IT contest

HCMC, Vietnam

2018 First Prize, HCMUS "Young Citizen's Idols" Drama contest

HCMC, Vietnam

Experience _____

Predicting Health Care Costs

HCMUS, Vietnam

Jupyter Notebook, Scikit-learn

May. 2021 - May. 2021

- Description:
 - Predict Health Care Costs via BMI, Height, Weight, is smoke, gender.
 - Make some EDA.
 - implement Linear Regression.
 - implement Random Forest Regression.
 - implement Gradient Boosting Algorithm.
- · Reponsibilities:
 - Planing
 - make som EDA.
 - implement Gradient Boosting Regression.

Python, Prolog, First-order Logic, DFS

Nov. 2020 - Nov. 2020

- · Description:
 - implement Prolog programming language
 - Design Knownledge base (facts and rules) of British Royal family tree.
 - Run some query to test the algorithm.
- Team size: 3
- · Position: Leader & Developer
- · Reponsibilities:
 - Planing
 - Implement Prolog
 - Implement design facts and queries for testing

Face Recognition HCMUS, Vietnam

GOOGLE COLAB, PYTHON, TENSORFLOW, RESEACH

- · Description:
 - Research some basic technique in Face Recognition (PCA, LDA, SVM,..).
 - Research for some Dataset for Face Recognition problem.
 - Research for a state of the art method in Face Recognition.
 - Run a simple demo (No need to self-implementation)
- · Team size: 3
- Position: Leader & Developer
- · Reponsibilities:
 - Planing
 - Research for CNN (Convolutional Neural Network)
 - Research for ResNet (Residual Network)
 - Research for ArcFace (Additive Angular Margin Loss)
 - Run demo (Not my implementation)

Covid-19 Visualization HCMUS, Vietnam

TABLEAU, JUPYTER NOTEBOOK, PANDAS, NUMPY, MATPLOTLIB

• Description:

- Crawl covid-19 data from worldometers website.
- Analyze and visualize using Jupiter Notebook.
- Analyze and visualize using Tableau.
- Team size: 5
- Position: Leader, Designer & Developer
- Reponsibilities:
 - Planing
 - Crawl data
 - Preprocessing
 - Compute and Visualize Correlation Matrix
 - Implement linear regression for 2, 3, 4 variables.Visualize scatter-plot and regression line of 2 variables.
 - Visualize data by worldmap with countries' longitude and latitude.
 - Draw Stacked Bar Chart for Total Case, Death Case, Active Case and Recovered Case by matplotlib.
 - Draw worldmap, bar char by Tableau.

Data Mining HCMUS, Vietnam

Jupyter Notebook, Weka, Pandas, Numpy, Matplotlib

Dec. 2020

May. 2021 - May. 2021

May. 2021 - May. 2021

- · Description:
 - Preprocess house-price dataset using Weka & Python (Count, fill missing data, normalization,...)
 - Analyzed data and Mining association rules in churn dataset using Apriori algorithm
 - Classified hawks dataset by Naive Bayes, Decision Tree using Weka and clustered iris dataset by K-Means and K-Medoids using Python.
- Team size: 2
- Position: Leader & Developer
- Reponsibilities:
 - Planing
 - Tuning Decision Tree in Weka
 - Tuning Apriori algorithm in Weka
 - Implement K-Mean and K-Medoids in Python

JUNE 23, 2021 NGO PHU HUU DAI SON · RESUME